you guys this thing has been brewing in
my soul since the first day I was
minding my business and somebody sent me
the very first video Pastor have you
seen this it's been brewing in my soul
so
listen if if I've come across as
passionate and if I've said anything
that was offensive in any way please
accept my apology right I'm not trying
to be offensive and I'm not trying to be
crude in any way and listen some of like
some of you are like Pastor you know
don't defend this is not about defending
myself right there are many people who
have questions many people who are
genuinely confused many young Adventists
that were like wait do we believe that
and and many non Adventists like wait I
know Adventists and they're pretty good
people do y'all believe that
right God calls us to stand for
truth so so let me not divert on this
too long all I'm simply saying
is if you see me being very passionate
please just understand right this is not
personal for me but it is personal for
me because truth is personal for me
right every one of those guys Mason is a
soul that that that that wants to be
saved I believe El's a soul that wants
to be saved we're all looking and
seeking and want wanting to make sure
that we are in the truth and following
the truth and sometimes your own
convictions can lead you to fight
against something that you don't even re
realize you're fighting against so Paul
why are you kicking against the Pricks
MH so so
again I'm just
asking grant me
that that you know I'm
human and listen y'all y'all know my
testimony from being out in the world
was somebody came from our crew it was
like no we're not doing that and y'all
are coming for my
crew right and and and the thing is you
know it's not me that anyone of any one
of of of my crew my ex-men my Christian
brothers and sisters any one of them
could do what I'm doing tonight right
any one of them some of you like hey
Pastor y start have y'all can see I have
so much to say right now I was like if
we bring somebody else on they will have
the same amount of stuff to and we'll
just never get anything done that's why
he brought me and that's why I was like
tante you come on and just monitor me
and but where going to follow up on this
and and and we're going to have other
people on like I we still there's going
to be a group of us that come together
you know like somebody said there's a
series Brewing I do believe there's a
series Brewing it's gonna happen it's
gonna happen and I like to tell people
that and just since we're on your your
this passion side taking just a little
break from all of that um I like a
little break a little break it's not
long it's a little break it's a little
break um just that this is the study of
God's word and connecting the dots and
proving the truth in God's word this is
his basketball this is his football this
is his you fill in the blank of people
when they get very passionate about you
know most men and and women can you know
are heavily into those to those sporting
events or those activities and they get
very passionate about it this is Pastor
Myers basketball and football and I can
I can yeah and you're SE and you're
seeing some very pent up cuz it's been
pinned up y'all I've been waiting for
the opportunity and I wish that we were
able to do this on the Perry's podcast
with Perry because I think presle is the
kind of guy that we could have sat down
and been like all right and he could
have just been like so all right they
said this but what do you know without
that debating spirit cuz often debates
don't get anywhere no is you know
someone said your side is always going
to think you win the other side is
always going to think they but to just
sit down with Preston and been like hey
so actually hears what we believe no we
don't believe that I think PR would have
been like ah okay I didn't know that man
I was anyway let's go to fact check
number six y'all yeah the Adventists
have an official Bible called the clear
word you heard him say it didn't we
remember that already we didn't we just
covered that the clear word does not
demote Jesus oh okay okay so now let's
see about the clear word when the clear
word was first published in 1994 the
general conference president president
made the following statement which was
published in the Adventist review the
7th Day Adventist Church does not limit
the various meaningful Avenues through
which its members study the scriptures
and we would hope that Dr Blanco's
significant personal effort would
contribute to this purpose as well those
who read it prayerfully should receive a
blessing from it just as they do from
any other paraphrases of the Bible the
Bible should in no way be considered or
this Bible should in no way be
considered an official Seventh Day
Advent his Bible nor did Dr Blanco
intend for it to be considered as such
Adventists do not have another Bible no
we do not the Ministerial Association of
the General Conference also produced a
statement in
1994 they said this the clear word is
not actually a Bible but a paraphrase
commentary that when properly used can
enrich one's devotional study and be
recommended in that way it should not be
used as the word of God for teaching
purposes to minimize the potential for
confu for confusing the clear word with
an actual Bible we recommend that it not
be used for preaching purpos or for
preaching from the pulpit or in teaching
Sabbath
school come on
y'all I I can read on but I'm not going
to I need y'all to understand Dr Blanco
says himself in an interview with author
Jack Blanco shortly after the clearw
Bible was released he was asked do we
now have an Adventist Bible his he
responded in the following way no that
certainly wasn't the intention and if
anybody said that this is an Adventist
Bible I would feel most
hurt guys not
it is not an Adventist
Bible you can't just put false
information out there like this and not
expect that people are going to say
present the
receipts this is
dishonesty and I'm trying to say that
nicely but you guys you know you may not
believe that the Ten Commandments still
stand you may not believe the Sabbath
still stand but certainly you believe
Thou shalt not bear false witness still
stands right certainly that's got to
still be a Christian principle
mhm
so
false fact check number one 2 3 4 five 6
7 false six false yeah fact check number
seven this will be a quick one SD
believed Ellen White was infallible
until the 1950s y'all heard that
statement right yeah he did sda's
believe that Ellen White was infallible
until the
1950s and yet um here we go that that's
them saying that I'm just a lot of what
the Adventist Church does is
that uh and here we go this is uh an
1854 statements of belief here's number
three that the holy scriptures of the
Old and New Testaments were given by
inspiration of God contain a full
revelation of his will to man and are
the only infallible rule of faith and
practice so how is it possible that the
church officially believed or
unofficially believed that Adventist uh
that that Ellen White was infallible
until the
1950s when in
1854 we were stting that the Bible is
the only infallible rule of
faith we are fact check
all night you guys I mean no not all
night we've been factchecking for this
whole PR